

 \bowtie

wzhu66@hku.hk



Sai Wan, Hong Kong



+852 52260730



https://weizhudesign.github.io/

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5

CSS

Javascript

Wordpress

Moodle

Microsoft Office Set

jQuery

PHP

MySQL

Node JS

LANGUAGES

Mandarin (native speaker)























WEI ZHU (Joe)

Web Developer & Multimedia Designer

Professional, task-driven web developer with 3 years experience in front end development and 5+ years in Art and Design. Proficient in developing user inferface, improving user experience, designing databases, writing and testing codes, troubleshooting all different issues related to web.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web developer/Graphic designer (Assistant Multimedia Developement Officer)

Faculty of Social Sciences, the University of Hong Kong.

(06/2021 - present)

- Responsible for front end design and set up of an Virtual Learning & Teaching Platform (an one stop shop for faculty student and teachers).
- Setting up LearningLocker LRS(learning record store) system on Ubuntu system, which help tracking data collected in faculty online learning platform.
- Designing, setting and maintaining Faculty websites (especially projects funded by The Hong Kong Jockey Club Charities Trust).
- Establish Online Student Registration system for faculty events (front end and backend).

Multimedia Web Designer (Research Assistant I)

The Centre for Information Technology in Education, the University of Hong Kong (09/2020 - 05/2021)

- Work independently in website production and development (Wordpress & Static html site).
- Design graphic artwork such as poster, certificate design and infographic illustration.

EDUCATION

Royal College of Art (RCA), London (09/2013 - 07/2015)

MA, Ceramic and Glass

Tsinghua University, Beijing (08/2009 - 07/2013)

BA, Ceramic Art and Design

COURSES & TRAININGS

System Administration and IT Infrastructure Services

Coursera.org

The Complete PHP MYSQL Professional Course with 5 Projects

Udemy.com

Interactivity with JavaScript

Coursera.org

Advanced Styling with Responsive Design

Coursera.org